http://world-information.org/wio/privacy

World-Information.Org
World-Information.Org is committed to preserving your privacy and safeguarding any information that you submit. The following statement describes the general information-gathering and usage practices of our site.Information CollectedWe do not collect personally identifiable information on our web site or otherwise unless you choose to give it to us via an electronic mail message, a phone call, or by postal mail. Even when you choose to give us information, we keep it confidential.Disclosures World-Information.Org will not disclose any information we keep about you to anyone. We will not provide any of your personal information to third parties without your permission and will not sell, rent, share or otherwise disclose any personal information to third parties for purposes of marketing, advertising, or promotion.Referrers, IP Addresses, System InformationOur web server automatically gathers some of this information and World-Information.Org uses it for site statistical analysis and to perform routine system maintenance. We do not track individual visitors to our web site and will not use this information to attempt to identify your personal information.SecurityWhile no system can provide guaranteed security, we take reasonable efforts to keep information you provide to us secure, including encryption technology, and physical security at the location of the server where information is stored.Links to Other SitesOur web site includes hyperlinks to sites maintained or controlled by others. World-Information.Org is not responsible for and does not routinely screen, approve, review, or endorse the contents or use of any of the products or services that may be offered at those web sites. We advise you to review the individual privacy policies of the respective sites.Change of Privacy PolicyThe restrictions on the dissemination of personal information are not subject to change. Our policy is updated occasionally but the changes will not reduce the privacy protection of visitors. If there are changes made in the future they will not affect information already collected.If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of World-Information.Org, please contact:World-Information.OrgTemporary QuartersNeustiftgasse 17A-1070 Vienna, Austriaphone: ++ 43.1.522 18 34fax: ++ 43.1.522 50 58e-mail: privacy@world-information.orghttp://world-information.org
SITE SEARCH
privacy policy
